Megan Storie

4505 DUVALL ST AUSTIN, TX 78751 (432) 813-6765 MEGANSTORIE@GMAIL.COM

I am an experienced technical writer with a history of working in Tech and Higher Ed. I hold a B.A. in English and a master's degree in Technical Communication.

Skills

I am proficient in Camtasia, Jira, Confluence, Microsoft Word, Excel, and the Adobe suite. I possess exceptional writing, communication, and time management skills. With over two years of experience in technical writing, I understand the unique requirements of the tech industry, including creating detailed API documentation and comprehensive installation guides for various applications.

Experience

JUL 2022 - PRESENT

Appfire, **Burlington MS** - *Technical Writer*

- Developed end-to-end technical documentation covering the entirety of dozens of unique applications.
- Amended existing application documentation in a timely manner for updates/migrations.
- Cross-communication expert dealing with Engineering, Customer Sat, and Marketing teams concurrently to always ensure the right messaging is public-facing.

OCT 2018 - JUN 2022

University of North Texas, Denton TX - Development Coordinator

- Implemented a stewardship program in the liberal arts college at UNT, connecting hundreds of donors with their scholarship recipients.
- Managed communications across the liberal arts college between the departments and development team.

NOV 2017 - AUG 2018

TIAA Bank, Lewisville TX - Banking Consultant

- Navigated several banking administrative systems to service clients' accounts.
- Assisted clients in opening new accounts with the company.

Education

2019 - 2022

University of North Texas, Denton TX - M.A. in Technical Communication

2009 - 2013

University of North Texas, Denton TX - B.A. in English